Most traders don't lose money on bad charts. They lose it buying euphoria, and selling fear.
Euphoria is an AI platform for BNB Chain that measures the emotion driving the market — not just the price.
Ask it about any token, and five agents go to work.
Scout reads the data; Narrative explains why it's moving.
Crowd scores the FOMO while Reverse argues the contrarian case.
Then the Judge delivers a verdict — buy, sell, or watch — with full reasoning, every signal traced to its source.
And it's not just talk — we turned that thesis into a deterministic, backtestable strategy.
Ride momentum, move to cash when the crowd turns euphoric or fearful.
On Bitcoin it beat buy & hold through a 30% crash, with a fraction of the drawdown.
The edge holds across the BNB ecosystem.
On PancakeSwap's CAKE and BNB itself, Euphoria preserved capital while buy & hold bled out.
Pure, reproducible, and unit-tested — powered by CoinMarketCap.
Euphoria. Trade market emotions, not charts. Built for BNB Hack.